ADIYANSAH S.KOM

Tambun Selatan, Bekasi Phone: +6287741413213

Email: adiyansahcode@gmail.com



About Me

I am a Developer. I have become a web developer since 2014. At the beginning of my career i use Codeigniter in my project, then I use the PHP Phalcon as a backend in my project, and I also used the Java Spring in my project. and now I am a backend developer who understands the Restful API. I can also analyze a problem and then make into a database design and system design.

Skill & Expertise

PHP Developer:	
JavaScript Developer:	_
Backend Developer:	
Database Analyst:	_
System Analyst:	_
Data Analyst:	_

Work Experience

Web Developer on PT. Prima Tangguh Abadi

October 2015 - March 2016

Analyze and creating a ERP system with Codeigniter and SQL Server.

Web Developer on PT. Loka Citra Media

April 2016 – July 2018

Analyze and creating a Web-Base system with Codeigniter and MySQL.

Backend Developer on PT. Sigma Cipta Caraka

August 2018 – August 2020

Analyze and creating RESTful Web Services with Phalcon and Java Spring.

Education

AMIK BINA SARANA INFORMATIKA, BEKASI

Manajemen Informatika D3

2011 - 2014

STMIK NUSA MANDIRI, JAKARTA

Sistem Informasi S1 2014 - 2015

PORTOFOLIO

1. Project Link2bos.com

Owner : PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Industry : MLM System

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

2. Project IbosAcademy.com

Owner : PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Industry: MLM System

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

3. Project Hirest

Owner : TelkomSigma

Industry : Information and Telecommunication Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

4. Project MBike

Owner : TelkomSigma

Industry : Information and Telecommunication Role : Backend Developer (Java Spring)

5. Project NSAM Enhancement and BroFist

Owner : Telkomsel Industry : Analytic Tools

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)









